Guide to the Beecher Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1806-1818, 1822-1849, (1850-1930), 1931-1948, 1964; Series I; 19' (46 boxes)
  - Beecher-Scoville Family Correspondence
    - Scoville, Annie Beecher
      - To A. B. S.:
        - Riggs, Louisa Irvine (fragment), undated (Box 27, Folder 1250)
        - Riggs, Thomas Lawrence, 1902-1905 (Box 27, Folder 1251)
        - Riggs, Thomas Lawrence (fragments), undated (Box 27, Folder 1252)
        - Rintoul, Mary Barry, undated (Box 27, Folder 1253)
        - Robinson, Eloise, 1918 (Box 27, Folder 1254)
        - Roe, Rev. Walter C. (Box 27, Folder 1255)
          See: Box 27, Folder 1178
        - Rogers, Eliza, undated (Box 27, Folder 1256)
        - Rogers, Fanny Smith, undated (Box 27, Folder 1257)
        - Rogers, Will, 1882 (Box 27, Folder 1258)
        - Rohlfs, Charles, 1927 (Box 27, Folder 1259)
        - Rollason, Herbert D., undated (Box 27, Folder 1260)
        - Root, Lyman C., 1911 (Box 27, Folder 1261)
        - Root, T.H., 1893 (Box 27, Folder 1262)
        - Rosa, Mary, 1927 (Box 28, Folder 1263)
        - Rose, Charlie, undated (Box 28, Folder 1264)
        - Roshery, Rosamund, undated (Box 28, Folder 1265)
        - Ross, Amos, 1901 (Box 28, Folder 1266)
        - Ross, Lucy G., 1902 (Box 28, Folder 1267)
        - Rotary Club of Stamford, Connecticut, 1924 (Box 28, Folder 1268)
        - Rouillard, David, 1896 (Box 28, Folder 1269)
        - Rowell, Doris, 1944, undated (Box 28, Folder 1270)
        - Rowley, Gertrude, 1887 (Box 28, Folder 1271)
        - Ryder, Rev. C.J., 1902, undated (Box 28, Folder 1272)
        - Ryder, Charles J., 1943 (Box 28, Folder 1273)
        - Sac and Fox Tribe. (Box 28, Folder 1274)
          See: Box 22, Folders 915-916 Box 26, Folders 1098-1102
        - Saint Margaret's School, 1926 February 17 (Box 28, Folder 1275)
        - Sanford, Dan (fragments), undated (Box 28, Folder 1276)
        - Schieffelin, M. Luise, 1922-1930 (Box 28, Folder 1277)
        - Schuck, Barbara Kelsey (fragment), undated (Box 28, Folder 1278)
        - Scoville, Alice T., 1933 June (Box 28, Folder 1279)
        - Scoville, Harriet E.G., 1872 (Box 28, Folder 1280)
        - Scoville, Harriet E.B., 1881-1883 Jan, 1883 June-Dec, 1884 February-June, 1884 September-1889, 1890 May-Nov, 1891-1900 (Box 28, Folder 1281-1298)
        - Scoville, Harriet E.B., 1901-1906, undated (Box 29, Folder 1299-1301)
        - Scoville, Gurdon Trumbull, 1931-1947 undated (Box 29, Folder 1302)
        - Scoville, Katharine, 1901-1930 (Box 29, Folder 1303)
        - Scoville, Laura, undated (Box 29, Folder 1304)
        - [Scoville, Louise] (niece) (fragments), 1924-[1946] undated (Box 29, Folder 1305)
        - Scoville, Louise (Armstrong), 1896 May-1898 Jul, 1899 May-1901 May, 1902 May-1903 May, 1903 December-1909, 1911-1947, undated (Box 29, Folder 1306-1316)
        - Scoville, Louise (Armstrong) (fragments), undated (Box 29, Folder 1317)
        - Scoville, Macon I., 1883-1885 (Box 29, Folder 1318)
        - Scoville, Marian (Aunt), undated (Box 29, Folder 1319)
        - Scoville, Rev. Samuel, 1881-1901, undated (Box 30, Folder 1320-1332)
        - Scoville, Samuel Jr., 1882-1898, 1901-1905 (Box 30, Folder 1333-1336)
        - Scoville, Samuel Jr., including Cooper, Hugh L. correspondence and Elliot, Silas Jr., 1905 (Box 30, Folder 1337)
        - Scoville, Samuel Jr., 1906-1933 November 9, 1933 November 15, 1933 November 25-1939, 1941-1949, undated (Box 30, Folder 1338-1344)
        - Scoville, Samuel, Jr. (fragments), undated (Box 31, Folder 1345)
        - Scoville, Samuel, Jr., 1882 (Box 31, Folder 1346)
        - Scoville, Samuel Armstrong, 1927-1947, undated (Box 31, Folder 1347)
        - Scoville, Samuel R., 1883-1898, undated (Box 31, Folder 1348)
        - Scoville, William Beecher, 1937-1941 (Box 31, Folder 1349)
        - Scoville, William Herbert, 1882-1898 Mar, 1898 May-1943, undated (Box 31, Folder 1350-1367)
        - Scoville, William Herbert (fragments), undated (Box 32, Folder 1368)
        - Scudder, Rev. L. W., 1906 (Box 32, Folder 1369)
        - Secomb, Mary T., 1895 (Box 32, Folder 1370)
        - Sequoya League, 1903 (Box 32, Folder 1371)
        - Seton, Ernest Thomson, 1903, May 22 (Box 32, Folder 1372)
        - Shackford, Martha Hale, 1924 (Box 32, Folder 1373)
        - Shaw, Effe G., 1892 (Box 32, Folder 1374)
        - Sherrill, Elmer, [1911], undated (Box 32, Folder 1375)
        - Shipley, Florence M., 1949 (Box 32, Folder 1376)
        - Shurtleff, W. P., 1930 (Box 32, Folder 1377)
        - Silent Automatic Sales Corporation, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 1378)
        - Sioux Tribe. (Box 32, Folder 1379)
          See: Box 19, Folders 777-779 Box 24, Folders 985-986 Box 25, Folders 1081-1085
        - Skenandore, Eli, 1901 (Box 32, Folder 1380)
        - Skenandore, N. J., undated (Box 32, Folder 1381)
        - Skenandore, W., 1893 (Box 32, Folder 1382)
        - Slocum, William F., 1898 (Box 32, Folder 1383)
        - Small, W., 1899 (Box 32, Folder 1384)
        - Smiley, Mabel C., 1930 (Box 32, Folder 1385)
        - Smith, Junius, 1911-1912 (Box 32, Folder 1386)
        - Smith, M. Virginia, 1887 (Box 32, Folder 1387)
        - Smith, Mary D., 1905-1923, undated (Box 32, Folder 1388)
        - Smith, Mary D. (fragment), undated (Box 32, Folder 1389)
        - Smith, Truman, undated (Box 32, Folder 1390)
        - Smith College Association for Christian Work, 1915 (Box 32, Folder 1391)
        - Smithsonian Institution, Bureau of American Ethnology, 1899 (Box 32, Folder 1392)
        - Soule, Eva L., 1890-1891 (Box 32, Folder 1393)
        - Soule, Harriet, 1936-1943, 1945-1948 undated (Box 32, Folder 1394-1395)
        - Soule, Harriet (fragments), undated (Box 32, Folder 1396)
        - Soule, Mabel W., 1890 (Box 32, Folder 1397)
        - Soule, Mary Lewis, 1930 (Box 32, Folder 1398)
        - Southern New England Telephone Company, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 1399)
        - Southern Workman, 1925 (Box 32, Folder 1400)
        - Southwest Indian Conference, 1910 (Box 32, Folder 1401)
        - Spaling, Emeline Ralmer, 1931 (Box 32, Folder 1402)
        - Squire, Alice Wolcott, 1919 April 18 (Box 32, Folder 1403)
        - Stamford, Connecticut Post Office, 1899 (Box 32, Folder 1404)
        - Stamford Historical Society, 1945, undated (Box 32, Folder 1405)
        - Stamford Inter-Faith Council, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 1406)
        - State Charities Aid Association, Placing-out Agency, 1914 (Box 32, Folder 1407)
        - Stewart, George, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 1408)
        - Steward, Lucy S., 1928 (Box 32, Folder 1409)
        - Steyert, R.A., undated (Box 32, Folder 1410)
        - Stone, Junius H., 1881-1888 (Box 32, Folder 1411)
        - Storrs Agricultural College, Storrs, Conn., 1897 (Box 32, Folder 1412)
        - Stowe, Katharine B., 1887 (Box 32, Folder 1413)
        - Stowe, Lyman Beecher, 1926-1943 (Box 32, Folder 1414)
        - Stranahan, Elizabeth A., 1899 (Box 32, Folder 1415)
        - Study Club, The, 1925 (Box 32, Folder 1416)
        - Stumpp and Walter Co., 1949 (Box 32, Folder 1417)
        - Swan and Moore, 1912 (Box 32, Folder 1418)
        - Taylor, Mary Alice, 1895-1930, undated (Box 33, Folder 1419)
        - Terry, Dame Ellen, undated (Box 33, Folder 1420)
        - Thacher, Emma, 1928, undated (Box 33, Folder 1421)
        - Thayer, Albert H., undated (Box 33, Folder 1422)
        - Thayer, Emma (Beach), 1914-1923 (Box 33, Folder 1423)
        - Thayer, Mrs. Horace H., Jr., undated (Box 33, Folder 1424)
        - Thompson, 1902 (Box 33, Folder 1425)
        - Thompson, Fred F., 1882-1886, undated (Box 33, Folder 1426)
        - Thompson, Mary, 1884-1885 (Box 33, Folder 1427)
        - Thompson, Mollie, 1882-1884 (Box 33, Folder 1428)
        - Thompson, Norma Cornelia, 1887 (Box 33, Folder 1429)
        - Thorpe, Albert, 1927 (Box 33, Folder 1430)
        - Tinker, Chauncey Brewster, 1919 (Box 33, Folder 1431)
        - Torrance, Mrs. W.J., 1923 (Box 33, Folder 1432)
        - Tower, Jennie M. (fragment), undated (Box 33, Folder 1433)
        - Tuttle, Daniel (B.P.), 1899 (Box 33, Folder 1434)
        - Tuttle, Rev. John Ellery, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 1435)
        - Tweedy, Henry Hallam, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 1436)
        - U. S. Department of Interior, 1905 (Box 33, Folder 1437)
        - U. S. Department of Interior Commissioner of Indian Affairs, 1901-05 May, 1905 June-1906 March (Box 33, Folder 1438-1440)
        - U. S. Department of Interior, Office of Indian Affairs., 1902-1905 (Box 33, Folder 1441)
          See also: Box 21, Folder 846 Box 26, Folder 1110
        - U. S. Department of the Interior U. S. Indian Service, 1900-1906 (Box 33, Folder 1442)
        - U. S. Department of the Interior, U. S. Indian Service. (Box 33, Folder 1443)
          See: Box 26, Folder 1097 Box 82, Folders 129-130 Box 22, Folder 881 Box 27, Folder 1212
        - U. S. Department of Interior U. S. Indian Service - Cheyenne Agency, 1898 (Box 33, Folder 1444)
        - U. S. Department of Interior U. S. Indian Service - Cheyenne River Agency, 1898 (Box 33, Folder 1445)
        - U. S. Department of Interior U. S. Indian Service - Omaha Agency, 1905 (Box 33, Folder 1446)
        - U. S. Department of Interior U. S. Indian Service - Sac and Fox Agency, 1897 (Box 33, Folder 1447)
        - U. S. Department of Interior U. S. Indian Service - Winnebago Agency, 1909 (Box 33, Folder 1448)
        - U. S. Department of Interior, U. S. Indian Service - Winnebago Agency. (Box 33, Folder 1449)
          See: Box 23, Folder 966 Box 25, Folder 1055
        - U. S. Department of Justice U. S. Attorney for Nebraska, 1905 (Box 33, Folder 1450)
        - U.S. Treasury Department Assistant Treasurer, U.S., undated (Box 33, Folder 1451)
        - U.S. Treasury Department Auditor for Department of Interior, 1906 (Box 33, Folder 1452)
        - U.S. Library of Congress, Card Division, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 1453)
        - U.S. Library of Congress, Librarian, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 1454)
        - U.S. Library of Congress Manuscripts Division, 1941-1948 (Box 33, Folder 1455)
        - Van Ausdal, Martha, 1927 (Box 33, Folder 1456)
        - Van Denburgh, Mrs. E.D., undated (Box 33, Folder 1457)
        - Van Salen, M.N., 1897 (Box 33, Folder 1458)
        - Vant, Alice Nelson, 1887 (Box 33, Folder 1459)
        - Vinal, S.H., 1924 (Box 33, Folder 1460)
        - Walker, Amos, 1895 (Box 33, Folder 1461)
        - Walker, J.G., 1904 (Box 33, Folder 1462)
        - Ward, Kate M., 1921 (Box 33, Folder 1463)
        - Warne, W.W. (Box 33, Folder 1464)
        - Warner, Ethel B., undated (Box 33, Folder 1465)
        - Warren, Kitty, 1926 (Box 33, Folder 1466)
        - Webster, Isaac K., 1897 (Box 33, Folder 1467)
        - Weinland, William H. (fragment), undated (Box 33, Folder 1468)
        - Well Spring, 1888 (Box 33, Folder 1469)
        - Welles, Anne Scoville, undated (Box 33, Folder 1470)
        - Wellesley Quarterly, 1913 (Box 33, Folder 1471)
        - Wellman, Arthur H., 1927-1932 (Box 33, Folder 1472)
        - Wendell, Edith G., undated (Box 33, Folder 1473)
        - West, John S., 1894 (Box 33, Folder 1474)
        - West Indies General Mission, 1929 (Box 33, Folder 1475)
        - Westchester Fire Insurance Co., 1943 (Box 33, Folder 1476)
        - Westtown School, Westtown, Pa., 1923 (Box 33, Folder 1477)
        - Weyman, Martha L., 1892 (Box 33, Folder 1478)
        - Whicher, George F., 1929 (Box 33, Folder 1479)
        - White Breast, 1906 (Box 33, Folder 1480)
        - White, Margaret H. (Beecher), 1888 (Box 33, Folder 1481)
        - Wierum, Anna Howard (Church), 1911 (Box 33, Folder 1482)
        - Willard S.B., undated (Box 33, Folder 1483)
        - Williams Margaret E., 1925 (Box 33, Folder 1484)
        - Willits, Katharine P., 1922-1923 (Box 33, Folder 1485)
        - Willits, Katharine P. (fragments), undated (Box 33, Folder 1486)
        - Wilson, John L., 1941 (Box 33, Folder 1487)
        - Wilson, Lucy Byles, 1923 (Box 33, Folder 1488)
        - Wistar, E.M., 1911 (Box 33, Folder 1489)
        - Wolcott, F.H., 1895 (Box 33, Folder 1490)
          (1491-1499 not assigned)
        - Woman's Board of Missions, 1924 (Box 33, Folder 1500)
        - Woman's Club of Orange, N.J., 1916 (Box 33, Folder 1501)
        - Woman's Club of Woodbury, Connecticut, 1921 (Box 33, Folder 1502)
        - Woody, Thomas, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 1503)
        - Woolsey, Jean E., 1943, undated (Box 33, Folder 1504)
        - Wright, Harriet E., 1937 (Box 33, Folder 1505)
        - Yale University, Alumni Registrar, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 1506)
        - Yale University Library, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 1507)
        - Younce, Seymour, 1898 (Box 34, Folder 1508)
        - Y.W.C.A. National Board, undated (Box 34, Folder 1509)
        - Scoville, Annie Beecher Memorandum on Work for Hampton, 1916 (Box 34, Folder 1510)
        - Y.M.C.A., Providence, R.I., 1925 (Box 34, Folder 1511)
        - Unidentified Indian Correspondents (Box 34, Folder 1512)
        - Unidentified (Box 34, Folder 1513-1518)
        - Scoville, Annie Beecher, Correspondence (fragments) (Box 34, Folder 1519)
      - From A.B.S.:
        - Armstrong, Samuel C. (1839-1893), 1889 (Box 34, Folder 1520)
        - Atlantic Monthly, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 1521)
        - Austin, H.P., 1927 (Box 34, Folder 1522)
        - Bacon, Theodore D., [1930], undated (Box 34, Folder 1523)
        - Bates, Katharine Lee. (Box 34, Folder 1524)
          See: Box 1, Folder 1
        - Beecher, Eunice W. (Bullard) (Box 34, Folder 1525)
          See: Box 4, Folder 205
        - Beecher, Henry Ward. (Box 34, Folder 1526)
          See: Box 14, Folders 565-566
        - Brennan, Jennie L., undated (Box 34, Folder 1527)
        - Bullard, F. Lauriston, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 1528)
        - Burgess, Mrs., undated (Box 34, Folder 1529)
        - Collins, Dr., 1928 (Box 34, Folder 1530)
        - Couteau, John Gauthier, 1912 (Box 34, Folder 1531)
        - Davidson, Mrs., 1928 (Box 34, Folder 1532)
        - Dinsmore, Charles A., 1928 (Box 34, Folder 1533)
        - Edgett, undated (Box 34, Folder 1534)
        - Frazier, George S., 1895 (Box 34, Folder 1535)
        - Grigg, Elmer, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 1536)
        - Hall, Rev. Charles, undated (Box 34, Folder 1537)
        - Holborn, Mrs. L. F., 1925 (Box 34, Folder 1538)
        - Holbrook, Florence, 1927 (Box 34, Folder 1539)
        - Loshe, Lotte, undated (Box 34, Folder 1540)
        - Mead, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 1541)
        - Nettleton, [Grace?], undated (Box 34, Folder 1542)
        - Packwood, Lahvesia, undated (Box 34, Folder 1543)
        - Plymouth Church, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 1544)
        - Pratt, Marion Root, 1920 (Box 34, Folder 1545)
        - Richardson, Lyon N., 1940 (Box 34, Folder 1546)
        - Sanders, Mrs., undated (Box 34, Folder 1547)
        - Editor, Saturday Review, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 1548)
        - Scoville, Annie Beecher, Memoranda on her investigations for Bureau of Indian Affairs, 1903, undated (Box 34, Folder 1549)
        - Scoville family members. (Box 34, Folder 1550)
          See: Box 18, Folder 684 Box 18, Folder 694 Box 18, Folder 704 Box 18, Folders 714-715 Box 42, Folders 1840-1862
        - Scoville, Harriet E. B. (Box 34, Folder 1551)
          See: Box 37, Folders 1676-1700
        - Stowe, Lyman Beecher, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 1552)
        - Tebo, Harrison (fragment), undated (Box 34, Folder 1553)
        - Twone, Mrs., undated (Box 34, Folder 1554)
        - U. S. Department of Interior, Commissioner of Indian Affairs, 1905 (Box 34, Folder 1555)
        - Wendell, Mrs., 1915 (Box 34, Folder 1556)
        - Winsor, Miss, 1916 (Box 34, Folder 1557)
        - Woolley, Miss, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 1558)
        - Unidentified (Box 34, Folder 1559)
        - Fragments (Box 34, Folder 1560)
    - Scoville, Harriet Eliza (Beecher)
      - To H. E. S.:
        - Abbott, Lyman, 1902 (Box 35, Folder 1561)
        - Allen, C. L., 1871 (Box 35, Folder 1562)
        - Allen, Rev. Paul Riley, 1908 (Box 35, Folder 1563)
        - Andrews, K. I., 1908-1909 (Box 35, Folder 1564)
        - Barber, Rachel A., 1908 (Box 35, Folder 1565)
        - Barton, William Sumner, 1898 (Box 35, Folder 1566)
        - Bates, Katharine Lee (1859-1929), 1888-1908, undated (Box 35, Folder 1567)
        - Beach, Chloe Buckingham, 1872, undated (Box 35, Folder 1568)
        - Beach, C. Y., 1908 (Box 35, Folder 1569)
        - Beach, Violet, 1897-1908 (Box 35, Folder 1570)
        - Beals, A. W., 1902 (Box 35, Folder 1571)
        - Bean, Fanny M., 1889 (Box 35, Folder 1572)
        - Beard, Augustus F., 1902 (Box 35, Folder 1573)
        - Beecher, Charles, [1894]-1899 (Box 35, Folder 1574)
        - Beecher, Eunice White (Bullard), 1863-1872, 1874-February 1876, 1876 June-1896, undated (Box 35, Folder 1575-1584)
        - Beecher, George Buckingham (1841-1925), 1902 (Box 35, Folder 1585)
        - Beecher, Harriet Leslie(?), 1902 (Box 35, Folder 1586)
        - Beecher, Harriet Jones (Benedict), 1864-1882, undated (Box 35, Folder 1587)
        - Beecher, Henry Barton, 1863-1897, undated (Box 35, Folder 1588-1589)
        - Beecher, Herbert Foote, 1902-1905 (Box 35, Folder 1590)
        - Beecher, Jessie Howe (Bigelow), undated (Box 35, Folder 1591)
        - Beecher, William Constantine, 1874-1902 (Box 35, Folder 1592)
        - Beecher, Schenck and Company, 1893 (Box 35, Folder 1593)
        - Bellows, Mrs., undated (Box 35, Folder 1594)
        - Bird, Sarah J., 1887-1902, undated (Box 35, Folder 1595)
        - Bliss, Howard S., 1902 (Box 35, Folder 1596)
        - Brown, (Aunt), 1869-1872, undated (Box 35, Folder 1597)
        - Bull, S.A., 1908 (Box 35, Folder 1598)
        - Bullard, Henry, 1908 (Box 35, Folder 1599)
        - Bullard, Jane H., 1869-1902, undated (Box 35, Folder 1600)
        - Bullard, Lizzie, 1877, undated (Box 35, Folder 1601)
        - Bullard, Louisa D., 1908 (Box 35, Folder 1602)
        - Bush, S.M., 1908 (Box 35, Folder 1603)
        - Caldwell, W.E., 1870 (Box 36, Folder 1604)
        - Chambers, James, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1605)
        - Chambers, Jessie I.B., 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1606)
        - Chapman, Fanny Reed, Chapman, R. Curtis, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1607)
        - Chapman, Mary E., 1902-1908 (Box 36, Folder 1608)
        - Chapman, W.P., 1908, undated (Box 36, Folder 1609)
        - Child, Rev. Frank S., 1902 (Box 36, Folder 1610)
        - Clarke, Margaret Stanton, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1611)
        - Clarke, William B, 1902 (Box 36, Folder 1612)
        - Cole, Maria, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1613)
        - Congregational Clerical Union of N.Y.C. and Vicinity, 1902 (Box 36, Folder 1614)
        - Crane, Esther M., 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1615)
        - Deane, Allen G., 1902 (Box 36, Folder 1616)
        - Dennis, Lucy Walton, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1617)
        - Devan, Harriet Beecher (Scoville), 1886, undated (Box 36, Folder 1618)
        - [Devan, Harriet], undated (Box 36, Folder 1619)
        - Devan, Harriet Beecher (Scoville) (fragments) (Box 36, Folder 1620)
        - Devan, Scoville, Thomas, 1908-1909 (Box 36, Folder 1621)
        - Devan, Spencer C., 1891 (Box 36, Folder 1622)
        - Eastman, Julia A, 1883-1908 (Box 36, Folder 1623)
        - Eaton, Rob and Maria, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1624)
        - Eilman, Kate P., undated (Box 36, Folder 1625)
        - Fenner, Mary B., 1887 (Box 36, Folder 1626)
        - Foote, Laura A., 1887 (Box 36, Folder 1627)
        - Ford, Mary Louisa, 1898-1902 (Box 36, Folder 1628)
        - Gold, Clara, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1629)
        - Grand Army of the Republic Hobbie Post, No. 23, 1902 (Box 36, Folder 1630)
        - Greene, Julia Warren, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1631)
        - Hague, Mary Ward, 1897 (Box 36, Folder 1632)
        - Hale, Edward Everett (1822-1909), 1902 (Box 36, Folder 1633)
        - Hale, Emily Baldwin (Perkins) (1829-, 1902 (Box 36, Folder 1634)
        - Halliday, Millie D., 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1635)
        - Hewitt, Harriet R., 1887 (Box 36, Folder 1636)
        - Hillis, Annie P., 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1637)
        - Hillis, Rev. Newell Dwight, 1902 (Box 36, Folder 1638)
        - Hooker, Isabella Homes (Beecher), 1860 (Box 36, Folder 1639)
        - Hostetter, Frances, undated (Box 36, Folder 1640)
        - Howard, Henry Ward Beecher, 1902 (Box 36, Folder 1641)
        - Howard, John Raymond (1837-1926), 1898-1905 (Box 36, Folder 1642)
        - Howard, Susan Taylor (Raymond), 1859-1893, 1896-1902, undated (Box 36, Folder 1643-1644)
        - Jewett, Annie F., 1870 (Box 36, Folder 1645)
        - Jewett, C.C., 1869 (Box 36, Folder 1646)
        - John Monroe and Co., 1859 (Box 36, Folder 1647)
        - Johnson, C. R., 1902-1908 (Box 36, Folder 1648)
        - Johnson, Frances, 1902 (Box 36, Folder 1649)
        - Ketchum, Jane Merritt, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 1650)
        - King, Essie (Howard) (fragment), undated (Box 36, Folder 1651)
        - King, Sarah W., 1892 (Box 36, Folder 1652)
        - King's Daughters, The, 1902 (Box 36, Folder 1653)
        - McCan, Agnes, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1654)
        - Miller, Samuel, 1902 (Box 36, Folder 1655)
        - Miller, T.D., 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1656)
        - Mitchell, C. D., 1898 (Box 36, Folder 1657)
        - Musser, J.H., 1902 (Box 36, Folder 1658)
        - Myers, Louise S., 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1659)
        - Nash, Alice, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1660)
        - Page, Curtis Hidden, 1902 (Box 36, Folder 1661)
        - Parker, Emma, 1887 (Box 36, Folder 1662)
        - Phelps, A.J., 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1663)
        - Plymouth Church, Brooklyn Young Men's Club, 1902 (Box 36, Folder 1664)
        - Plymouth Church, Brooklyn Young Women's Guild, 1902 (Box 36, Folder 1665)
        - Pond, James Burton (1838-1903), 1896 (Box 36, Folder 1666)
        - Powell, Anna Barton, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1667)
        - Pratt, Rev. Dwight Mallory, 1902 (Box 36, Folder 1668)
        - Pratt, Frances L., 1887 (Box 36, Folder 1669)
        - Preston, Marguerite, 1885 (Box 36, Folder 1670)
        - Price, Adelaide W., 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1671)
        - Raymond, Rossiter Worthington (1840-1918), 1898-1908 (Box 36, Folder 1672)
        - Reed, Mary B., 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1673)
        - Rice, Mrs. George W., 1908 (Box 36, Folder 1674)
        - Ritzinger, Myla (Fletcher), undated (Box 36, Folder 1675)
        - Scoville, Annie Beecher, 1871-1882 Mar, 1882 September-1884 Nov, 1885-1886 May, 1886 August-Nov, 1891-1901 June, 1903 June-1904 Oct, 1905 April-1909 June, 1909 August-1911, undated (Box 37, Folder 1676-1700)
        - Scoville, Eliza, 1898 (Box 38, Folder 1701)
        - Scoville, Mrs. Jacob, undated (Box 38, Folder 1702)
        - Scoville, Louise Hopkins (Armstrong), 1896-1910 (Box 38, Folder 1703)
        - Scoville, Maria, 1870-1911, undated (Box 38, Folder 1704)
        - Scoville, Rev. Samuel, 1864-1871, 1873-1879, 1882 February-March, 1881 August-Sept, 1882 April-Nov, 1883 August-1888, 1889 March-Sept, 1891-1898, 1899 July-August, 1900-1901 Oct, undated (Box 38, Folder 1705-1721)
        - Scoville, Samuel R., 1902 (Box 39, Folder 1722)
        - Scoville, Samuel Jr., 1888-1892, 1900-1911, undated (Box 39, Folder 1723-1726)
        - Scoville, William Herbert, 1888-1892 July (Box 39, Folder 1727)
        - Scoville, William Herbert, 1894-1911 (Box 39, Folder 1728)
        - Scudder, Rev. William H., 1902 (Box 39, Folder 1729)
        - Sedgwick, Katharine M., 1908 (Box 39, Folder 1730)
        - Sexton, Delia S., 1901 (Box 39, Folder 1731)
        - Shearman, Elmira, 1908 (Box 39, Folder 1732)
        - Smith, Annie (Morrill), 1902 (Box 39, Folder 1733)
        - Sparthawk, Minnie, 1902 (Box 39, Folder 1734)
        - Starr, Isabelle C., 1901 (Box 39, Folder 1735)
        - Stebbins, Belle K., 1908 (Box 39, Folder 1736)